<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>pabes</title>
    <link>https://pabes.me/</link>
    <description>Recent content on pabes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>©</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://pabes.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Smashing Your SANS Course</title>
      <link>https://pabes.me/smashing-your-sans-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pabes.me/smashing-your-sans-course/</guid>
      <description>Introduction If you&amp;rsquo;re reading this post, you likely know of the SANS course and associated GIAC certification. You&amp;rsquo;re likely about to sit your course and/or exam and are looking for some tips and tricks to maximise the amount of value you get out of this eye-wateringly expensive course. This post is an overview of the tips and tricks that I have for smashing your SANS GIAC experience.
At time of writing, I&amp;rsquo;ve been lucky enough to undertake FOR508: Advanced Incident Response, Threat Hunting, and Digital Forensics and SEC511: Continuous Monitoring and Security Operations and successfully pass both associated exams to become GCFA and GMON certified.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SOARing by the seat of your pants</title>
      <link>https://pabes.me/soaring-by-the-seat-of-your-pants/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pabes.me/soaring-by-the-seat-of-your-pants/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s a lot of hype with Security Orchestration, Automation and Response (SOAR) and on paper it basically sells itself. A product that improves Time To Respond (TTR) metrics whilst decreasing FTE count is a CISO&amp;rsquo;s wet dream. But unfortunately, many orgs find it difficult to realise value with their SOAR products and in a way are soaring by the seat of their pants.
This blog post provides some (no marketting) recommendations on how you can realise the most value from your SOAR investment.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>